Contact

ashutosh877@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashutoshkashyap (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Strategic Planning Web Development Machine Learning

Certifications

Certificate of Merit Machine Learning Introduction to C++ IEEE Xtreme Participant in Quiz

Honors-Awards

Algorithm Developer Top 10% Awardee

National Level Participant and Delhi State Winner

Inspire Award Candidate

Ashutosh Kashyap

TEDx Speaker | IIT, DU, NIT Jury & Panelist | Entrepreneur | PUBG Ace | Startup Guy | Traveller

New Delhi

Summary

Ashutosh is a student entrepreneur, 21 y/o and having experience in multiple domains with multiple start-ups.

He launched his first start-up in 2016 with an investment of INR 10k and reached profitability within 3 months. He also bagged an seed investment of undisclosed amount (Coz yahan amount liqhunga, to kuch to log kahenge)

Afterward, he has worked with several college entrepreneurs pan India. Currently, he is the founder of 3 profitably running start-ups, which were are all bootstrapped, that is without any external monetary support. He actively working with 4 other startups as a Cofounder, guiding them towards exponential growth.

He has worked with investment firms with angel investors and venture capitalists.

He is also running an incubator and accelerator program to support the Indian entrepreneurship ecosystem.

One of the start-ups, where he is Bussiness Development Head and co-founder, is already generating more than INR 4 cr in revenue.

His latest venture has earned revenue over INR 450K within 10 days of its inception (1 Jan 2020 to 11 Jan 2020), a startup centric IT and R&D firm, even without a website or office.

Due to commendable work ethics and proven track record, he has earned selection as a delegate to participate in MIT Bootcamps (organized by Massachusetts Institute of Technology) twice, for :

- 1. Innovation and Enterprunerhsip
- 2. Technology and Enterprunerhsip

He has been invited as a guest speaker in multiple educational institutions on the likes of IIIT Gwalior, DU, GGSIPU, NIT Durgapur, etc.

He has partnered with NGOs to assist in the improvement of their operational efficiencies.

He is on a mission to improve the efficiency of student entrepreneurs and to enable self-sufficiency through bootstrapping and reducing the dependability on external investments. He is actively working towards preventing startups from being conned by fraudsters in the start-up ecosystem.

Experience

Decibell
Growth Manager
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
New Delhi, Delhi, India

Ashutosh Kashyap Enterprises LLP Founder December 2019 - Present (9 months) New Delhi Area, India

MyMedicineBox Business Development Executive November 2019 - May 2020 (7 months) New Delhi Area, India

Startup Monk
7 months

Business Development Executive
August 2019 - February 2020 (7 months)
New Delhi Area, India

UI and UX Designer August 2019 - August 2019 (1 month) New Delhi Area, India Non Binary Analytics and Co. Founder and COO June 2019 - February 2020 (9 months)

New Delhi Area, India

The Capital Wizards

4 months

Business Development Executive September 2019 - November 2019 (3 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Chief Marketing Officer

August 2019 - September 2019 (2 months)

New Delhi Area, India

ESSCOM Education

Machine Learning Trainee
June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Triple I business services Pvt. Ltd.
Bussiness and Sales Development Intern
June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Cognoscente Invnted Pvt Ltd Software Trainee

May 2019 - July 2019 (3 months)

Noida Area, India

Innovation and Incubation Club ADGITM

President and Founder

June 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 2 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Carrer Gurukul

Instructor of Computer Awareness

May 2019 - June 2019 (2 months)

New Delhi Area, India

Get Set Resumes

Business Development Intern January 2019 - April 2019 (4 months)

New Delhi Area, India

TripyWorld Business Development Intern October 2018 - April 2019 (7 months)

New Delhi Area, India

MIT Bootcamps

3 months

Selected as Delegate
January 2019 - March 2019 (3 months)

Tokyo, Japan

Selected as Delegate

January 2019 - February 2019 (2 months)

Brisbane, Australia

Selected at MIT Bootcamp on the topic of Innovation and Enterprenership , by MIT Bootcamp Admission team.

Shanons

Bussiness Development Intern December 2018 - March 2019 (4 months)

New Delhi Area, India

IEEE

IEEE External Affairs Head January 2018 - January 2019 (1 year 1 month) New Delhi Area, India

ReadersCrib
Sales And Marketing Intern
July 2018 - September 2018 (3 months)
New Delhi Area, India

Connect My Edu Founder August 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 1 month) New Delhi Area, India Smart India Hackathon 2018 Algorithm Developer March 2018 - March 2018 (1 month) CSIR, Pune

Secured All India Rank 3 in under CSIR department.

I started with the Idea to make an App that will give the risk factor of Dengue to any Smartphone owner In real time.

Submitted the App in Smart India Hackathon

Selected In the Grand Finale of SIH 2018, for team Pesky Mosquito.

Developed the Algorithm to run the Application that was built.

The Algorithm used Machine Learning and also Simple Coding to run the Application

Northern India Engineering College, New Delhi Technical Trainer in Python Language February 2018 - March 2018 (2 months)

New Delhi Area, India

We organised a workshop on Python and Machine Learning. It was a 7 day workshop, 2 hours each day. My role here was of the trainer. I used to teach students basics and advanced Python. About 120 students participated in the workshop. As it was not an official workshop, so i dont have certificates, but I do have the photos which I will be sharing here.

TAKSHILA FOUNDATION

Chemistry Teacher September 2017 - December 2017 (4 months) Janakpuri, New Delhi, India

I worked With students of Class 8, Class 9 and Class 10. It gave me experience with Students of age group 14 to 16. I used that Knowledge In my Start Up also.

IEEE

Publicity Coordinator
July 2017 - November 2017 (5 months)

New Delhi Area, India

I used to manage the Offline and Online Publicity of the annual Event In IEEE. This gave me an experience about management and how to promote an event.

PINNACLE Coaching Classes Chemistry Faculty July 2016 - December 2016 (6 months) Kohat Enclave, New Delhi , India

Worked as Chemistry Faculty
Taught class 11th and Class 12th students for JEE chemistry
Took doubt classes too
Took 4 batches of students
Batch strengths used to be from 12 people to 16 people only

Education

Kendriya Vidyalaya

12th Paas, Physics , Chem , Maths , Computer Science \cdot (2003 - 2015)